Guide to the Larry Kramer Papers YCAL MSS 722
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- October 2008 Acquisition, circa 1916-2008; 344633; 100.63 Linear Feet (117 boxes) + 2 broadside folders, 8 rolls, 2 record albums
  - Computer media, 344637
    - TAP Day by Day, 2008-ycal-22518-0212; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - QUESTRONEX FORMATTER/INSTALLER StorageWare, 2008-ycal-22518-0213; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - Norton Emergency (+ System Startup), 2008-ycal-22518-0214; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - WORDPERFECT FOR THE MACINTOSH Installer 2.1, 2008-ycal-22518-0215; 1 3.5_floppy_disks (Box 179)
    - [no label information], 2008-ycal-22518-0238; 1 ZIP Disks; 250640384 bytes 250.64 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 181)
  - Previously restricted papers, circa 1990-1996; 344634
    - Drafts of "The American People", undated; 344636; 0 See Container Summary 14 folders (Box 182)
    - Drafts of "The American People", undated; 344635; 0 See Container Summary 2 folders (Box 183)
    - Writing files for "Flesh and Blood", circa 1995 (Box 183)
    - Writing files for "The American People", circa 1990-1996; 0 See Container Summary 2 folders (Box 183)
    - Drafts of "Searching For My Heart No Longer", undated; 0 See Container Summary 5 folders (Box 183)
    - Tax information, circa 2007-2008 (Box 234)
- July 2011 Acquisition, 2007-2011; 344578; 3.71 Linear Feet (8 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  Organized into three series: I. Correspondence. II. Writings. III. Personal and Other Papers.
  - Correspondence, 1; 344631
    - Unsorted Correspondence, 1999-2011; 344632; 23 Folders (Box 187)
  - Writings, 2; 344619
    - "Chapter 6: The curious case of Elmer Ellsworth," typescript, 2003; 344630 (Box 188)
    - "Chapter 7: Yours forever," typescript, 2003; 344629 (Box 188)
    - "Chapter 8: Marriage and Mary Todd," typescript, 2003; 344628 (Box 188)
    - "Chapter 9: Lincoln in perspective--three views," typescript, 2003; 344627 (Box 188)
    - "Homosexuals in Colonial America," draft, undated; 344626 (Box 188)
    - "The Normal Heart," revised typescripts and associated materials, 2004; 344625 (Box 188)
    - "We are not crumbs; we must not accept crumbs," speech, typescript, 2007; 344624 (Box 188)
    - "I wanted to look at water...," drafts, undated; 344623 (Box 188)
    - "Obama is not my president.." speech, typescript, 2010; 344622 (Box 188)
    - "Lambda Awards," speech, typescipt, 2010; 344621 (Box 188)
    - Notebooks, undated; 344620; 2 Folders (Box 188)
  - Personal and Other Papers, 2001-2011; 3; 344586
    - Personal, 344611
      - Medical-Family-Friends-Contacts, 2001; 344618; 2 Folders (Box 188)
      - "Lee Pace," drawing, 2011; 344617 (Box 188)
      - "Liza's 50th Birthday," printed photograph album, 2009; 344616 (Box 188)
      - Photographs, 2009; 344615 (Box 188)
      - Portrait of Larry Kramer, photographs, undated; 344614
      - Dog license, dog tags, 2011; 344613 (Box 188)
      - Realia, undated; 344612; 2 Folders (Box 188)
    - Financial Records, 2010; 344606
      - Royalties, 2008-2011; 344610 (Box 188)
      - Probate, 2008; 344609 (Box 188)
      - Taxes, 2008-2009; 344608; 3 Folders (Box 188)
      - Financial Records, 2008-2010; 344607; 3 Folders (Box 188)
    - Audio Visual Material, 2008-2009; 344600
      - "Excerpts from GMHC-Oral History," (CD), undated; 344605 (Box 189)
        - For Larry Excerpts from GMHC Oral History, 2011-ycal-45313-0001; 1 DVD-Rs; 645562368 bytes 645.56 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 189)
      - "Out-Q in the morning," (CD), 2 copies, 2008; 344604 (Box 189)
        - OutQ in the Morning with Larry Flick SHOW MASTER MONDAY DECEMBER 1, 2008 Featuring Keith Price and Cynthia Frawley WORLD AIDS DAY BROADCAST 2008 with LARRY KRAMER, 2011-ycal-45313-0002; 1 CD-Rs; 385673948 bytes 387.67 Megabytes. (Box 189)
        - OutQ in the Morning with Larry Flick SHOW MASTER MONDAY DECEMBER 1, 2008 Featuring Keith Price and Cynthia Frawley WORLD AIDS DAY BROADCAST 2008 with LARRY KRAMER, 2011-ycal-45313-0003; 1 CD-Rs; 385673948 bytes 387.67 Megabytes. (Box 189)
      - Ryo Toyonaga, artist drawings, (DVD), undated; 344603 (Box 189)
        - RYO TOYONAGA DRAWINGS, 2011-ycal-45313-0004; 1 DVD-RWs; 1164607488 bytes 1.16 Gigabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 189)
      - "Summer of the Stonewall," documentary, (DVD), 2009; 344602 (Box 189)
        - 40th Anniversary of Stonewall June 2009 | Episode 1809 Running Time: 57:42 IN THE LIFE, 2011-ycal-45313-0005; 1 DVD-Rs; 2791899136 bytes 2.79 Gigabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 189)
      - "Alan Ross, Texas Freedom parade," (DVD), 2009; 344601 (Box 189)
        - 2009 Alan Ross TEXAS FREEDOM PARADE 5:43 minutes Larry Kramer Honorary Grand Marshal, 2011-ycal-45313-0006; 1 DVD-RWs; 737869824 bytes 737.87 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 189)
    - Printed Material, 344587
      - AIDS material, 2009-2010; 344599 (Box 190)
      - Newsweek Magazine, 2006 May 15; 344598 (Box 190)
        "AIDS at 25, a special report," includes article with Larry Kramer
      - "Nuremberg Trials for Aids," printed version, copy, undated; 344597 (Box 190)
      - Playbill, 2004-2011; 344596 (Box 190)
      - Ryo Totonaga, printed artwork, 2005-2009; 344595; 2 Folders (Box 190)
        Includes art books and printed versions of Totanaga's artwork
      - "Visual and musical responses to the Aids Crisis in the U.S: heightening societal awareness and inciting political action." typescript by Kaitlyn Greer, 2009; 344594 (Box 190)
      - "Women in Love," screenplay by William Ivory, annotated by Larry Kramer, 2009; 344593 (Box 190)
      - Pamphlets, brochures, 2009-2011; 344592; 3 Folders (Box 190)
      - Posters, undated; 344591
      - Magazines, 2004-2011; 344590 (Box 190)
      - Unsorted material, 2008-2011; 344589; 4 Folders (Box 190)
      - Clippings, 2004-2011; 344588; 4 Folders (Box 190)
  - Oversize, 1974-2010; 344579
    - Portrait of Larry Kramer, photographs, undated; 344585 (Box 191 (Oversize))
    - Clippings, 1974-2009; 344584; 3 Folders (Box 192 (Oversize))
    - Posters, undated; 344583 (Box 192 (Oversize))
    - Poster, undated; 344582 (Box 193 (Broadside))
    - Framed Art, 2010; 344581 (Box 194 (Oversize))
    - T-Shirts, undated; 344580 (Box 195 (Oversize))
- February 2016 Acquisition, 1981-2015; 17.33 Linear Feet (17 boxes)
  Organized into five series: Writings, Writings by Others, Correspondence, Personal and Other Papers, Computer Media, and Audiovisual Material.
  https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bf4e0e2c-fca6-414f-911b-d036681133ba
  - Writings, 7.58 Linear Feet (7 boxes)
    - "AIDS: The war is lost", 1990 (Box 196)
    - "American People Volume 1" drafts and notes (16 folders), undated (Box 196)
    - "American People Volume 1" drafts and notes (18 folders), undated (Box 197)
    - "American People Volume 1" drafts and notes (4 folders), circa 2003 (Box 198)
    - "American People Volume 1" galley proof, circa 2003 (Box 198)
    - "Breeders 1" draft, undated (Box 198)
    - Book proposals, undated (Box 198)
    - "Faggots" draft (5 folders), 1999 (Box 198)
    - "Faggots" draft, 2000 (Box 198)
    - "Four Friends" typescript, undated (Box 198)
    - "Just Say No" notes, reviews, and clippings, 1990 (Box 198)
    - "Late Bloomers" screenplay, undated (Box 198)
    - "Masturbov Gardens" draft, 1990 (Box 199)
    - "Minor Dark Age" draft, undated (Box 199)
    - Miscellaneous writings and notes (2 folders), undated (Box 199)
    - "New Beginning" draft, undated (Box 199)
    - "Normal Heart" screenplay and drafts (20 folders), circa 1986 (Box 199)
    - "Search For My Heart No Longer" drafts (2 folders), circa 1991 (Box 199)
    - "Sissie's Scrapbook" screenplay, undated (Box 199)
    - "Sissie's Scrapbook" screenplay, undated (Box 200)
    - "Women in Love" screenplay and drafts (6 folders), 2001-2002 (Box 200)
  - Writings by others, 1.08 Linear Feet (1 box)
    - "Lincoln" screenplay, undated (Box 200)
    - "Chinatown" screenplay, undated (Box 200)
    - Berman, Marjorie. "Intersection of Agitprop Theatre and AIDS Activism..." thesis, 2013 (Box 200)
    - Galassi, Jonathan--song lyrics, undated (Box 200)
    - Kaufman, Moises. "Three trials of Oscar Wilde" playscript, 2015 (Box 200)
    - "'Dr. Strangelove" or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb" screenplay, undated (Box 200)
    - Newspapers, magazines, and printed material, 1984-2015; 0 See Container Summary 22 folders (Box 230)
    - Newspapers, magazines, and printed material, 1979-2015; 0 See Container Summary 8 folders (Box 231)
    - Newspapers, magazines, and printed material, 1970-2015; 0 See Container Summary 2 folders (Box 232)
  - Correspondence, personal and other papers, 3.92 Linear Feet (3 boxes)
    - Engraved dish/award for Rodger McFarlane from Gay Men's Health Crisis, 1982 (Box 200)
    - Esquire cover plaque/award, 1984 (Box 200)
    - 80th birthday cards and notes, 2015 (Box 200)
    - Bracelet, undated (Box 200)
    - Yale commencement programs and related papers, 2015 (Box 200)
    - Correspondence, 1982-2015; 0 See Container Summary 3 folders (Box 200)
    - Correspondence, 1985-2015; 0 See Container Summary 2 folders (Box 200)
    - Diary, undated (Box 200)
    - Wishengrad family tree, 1981 (Box 201)
    - Financial papers, 2012-2014 (Box 201)
    - Flyers, undated (Box 201)
    - Itineraries, 1987; 2015 (Box 201)
    - Rea Kramer personal papers, 1960-1983 (Box 201)
    - Rea Kramer passports, 1984; 1995 (Box 201)
    - Eulogy and notes for Rea Kramer's funeral, circa 1996 (Box 201)
    - Legal papers, 2008 (Box 201)
    - Medical papers, circa 2014 (Box 201)
    - Notes, undated (Box 201)
    - Event passes, undated (Box 201)
    - Photographs, 2001, undated; 0 See Container Summary 3 folders (Box 201)
    - Lapel pins, undated (Box 201)
    - Press releases, 1985-1987 (Box 201)
    - Research notes, circa 1987-1987, undated; 0 See Container Summary 2 folders (Box 201)
    - Speeches, circa 1987-2004; 0 See Container Summary 2 folders (Box 201)
    - Award certificates, 1993-2014 (Box 206)
    - New York Times newspapers, 1987 (Box 206)
    - Poster for Hotchkiss Gay/Straight Alliance event featuring Larry Kramer, 2013 (Box 206)
  - Computer media, 3.5 Linear Feet (4 boxes)
    Boxes 202-205 (digital media): Restricted Fragile Material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&dfa9fcd5-e7f6-4fb8-9e15-094cc1691f25
    - "(500) days of summer" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "9" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Alice in Wonderland" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "All Good Things" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "Animal Kingdom" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Anna Karenina" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 202)
    - "Another Year" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Avatar" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Anvil" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Beasts of the Southern Wild" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 202)
    - "Beginners" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 202)
    - "Bernie" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Better Life" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 202)
    - "Blue Valentine" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "Broken Embraces" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Brothers" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Capitalism: A Love Story" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Cars 2" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Channel Clublum Two 2004-2009" DVD (Box 202)
    - "Chasing Ice" screener CD (2 folders), 2012 (Box 202)
    - "Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Company Men" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "Coralina" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Crazy Heart" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Creation" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Disgrace" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 202)
    - "District 9" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Divo" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "End of Watch" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Eye of the Storm" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 202)
    - "Fair Game" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "Fighter" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 202)
    - "For Colored Girls" screener DVD (Box 202)
    - "For Greater Glory" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Funny People" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 202)
    - "Ginger and Rosa" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Girl with the Dragon Tattoo" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "The Grey" screener DVD, undated (Box 202)
    - "Half Nelson" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 202)
    - "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows Part II" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 203)
    - "Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Hunger Games" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Hurt Locker" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "I Am Love" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "I Love You Phillip Morris" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "Imaginarium of Dr. Parnassus" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "In the Loop" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Inception" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "Inglorious Basterds" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Inside Job" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "The Intouchables" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Invictus" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Irene in Time" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Hangover" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "How Do You Know" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - Jean-Luc Goddard Collection DVDs, 1982-1993 (Box 203)
    - "The Karate Kid" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "King's Speech" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "La Prima Cosa Bella" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Late Quartet" screener DVD, 2013 (Box 203)
    - "Lightkeepers" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Lincoln" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Looper" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Love + Other Drugs" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - Paramount screener DVD pack (Lovely Bones, Up in the Air, Star Trek), 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Master" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Mary and Max" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Me and Orson Welles" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 203)
    - "The Men Who Stare at Goats" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Les Miserables" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Moonrise Kingdom" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 203)
    - "Mother and Child" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "The Music Never Stopped" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 203)
    - "The Night Larry Kramer Kissed Me" DVD, 2011 (Box 203)
    - "No Country for Old Men" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 203)
    - "Out in the Silence" DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Outrage" DVDs (2 folders), 2009 (Box 203)
    - "Pirate Radio" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 203)
    - "The Pirates! Band of Misfits" screener DVD, undated (Box 203)
    - "Please Give" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 204)
    - "Pirates of the Caribbean on Stranger Tides" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 204)
    - "Precious" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "The Princess and the Frog" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Promised Land" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Quartet" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Running with Scissors" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 204)
    - "Salt" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Saving Grace B. Jones" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Sessions" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "A Serious Man" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 204)
    - "Shutter Island" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 204)
    - "Silver Linings Playbook" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "A Single Man" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 204)
    - "Skyfall" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Smashed" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Snow White and the Huntsman" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Spinetingler!" The William Castle Story" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Take Shelter" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Taking Woodstock" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Tangled" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Tempest" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "This is 40" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Tinker, Tailor, Solider, Spy" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 204)
    - "Touching Home" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 204)
    - "Two Lovers" screener DVD, 2009 (Box 204)
    - "Up" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "West of Memphis" screener DVD, 2012 (Box 204)
    - "Whatever Works" screener DVD, undated (Box 204)
    - "Win Win" screener DVD, 2011 (Box 204)
    - "Winter's Bone" screener DVD, 2010 (Box 204)
    - "The Wire" DVDs [Seasons 3-5], 2006-2008; 0 See Container Summary (3 folders) (Box 204)
    - "Wrangler" screener DVD, undated (Box 205)
    - "Zodiac" screener DVD, 2007 (Box 205)
    - "Irene in Time" soundtrack, 2009 (Box 205)
    - Conversation with Montgomery fellow: Larry Kramer, 2012
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8137096b-b89e-47f6-ab31-485c8f9eae1b
      - The Kenneth and Harle Montgomery Endowment presents A Conversation with Montgomery Fellow Larry Kramer January 23, 2012 Filene Auditorium, Moore Hall, 2016-ycal-0107-0001; 1 DVD-Rs (Box 205)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&126d2785-9adb-475c-abb8-764005534464
  - Audiovisual material, 0.42 Linear Feet (1 box)
    Restricted fragile material. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - "Question of Equality" VHS set, 1995 (Box 207)
      This VHS set is commercial. It has not been digitized.
- November 2016 Acquisition, 1960-2012; 20.67 Linear Feet (23 boxes)
  Organized into six series: Writings, Writings by others, Correspondence, Personal and other papers, Diaries and notebooks, Electronic media, and Audiovisual materials.
  - Writings, 2.92 Linear Feet (7 boxes)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 0 See Container Summary 5 folders (Box 208)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 0 See Container Summary 5 folders (Box 209)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 0 See Container Summary 4 folders (Box 210)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 0 See Container Summary 5 folders (Box 211)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 0 See Container Summary 6 folders (Box 212)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 0 See Container Summary 5 folders (Box 213)
    - "The American People" drafts and notes, undated; 0 See Container Summary 4 folders (Box 214)
    - "The Normal Heart" draft and notes, undated (Box 214)
  - Writings of others, 0.42 Linear Feet (1 box)
    - Black, Dustin Lance. "8" script, undated (Box 215)
    - Kramer, Arthur. "Memoir of an Ancient Yalie" draft, 2012 (Box 215)
  - Correspondence, personal papers, and photographs, 5.83 Linear Feet (10 boxes)
    Includes correspondence, event documentation, business and financial papers, theatrical programs, newsletters, press clippings, and personal papers.
    - Yale-related business papers, 2000-2001; 0 See Container Summary 2 folders (Box 215)
    - Business and financial papers, 1997-2008; 0 See Container Summary 6 folders (Box 216)
    - Business and financial papers, 1998-2012; 0 See Container Summary 5 folders (Box 217)
    - Business and financial papers, 1999-2013; 0 See Container Summary 6 folders (Box 218)
    - Correspondence, 1976-2016; 0 See Container Summary 5 folders (Box 219)
    - Architectural Digest article draft and notes, 1999 (Box 219)
      Includes drafts and research notes for an Architectural Digest article written by Larry Kramer.
    - Clippings and press, 2003-2016; 0 See Container Summary 2 folders (Box 219)
    - Clippings and press, 2009-2015 (Box 220)
    - Event flyers, undated (Box 220)
    - Event planning documentation, 2004-2007 (Box 220)
    - "Forum on Theatre for Public Health" program, 2011 (Box 220)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis newsletter, 1982 (Box 220)
    - Empty CD case for Dawn Upshaw's "I Wish It So", 1994 (Box 227)
    - "The Normal Heart" playbills and press clippings, 2011 (Box 220)
    - Obituaries and rolodex cards, circa 1989-1990 (Box 220)
    - Out 100, 2011 (Box 220)
    - Outer Critics Circle Award presented to Larry Kramer for "The Normal Heart" revival, 2011 (Box 220)
    - Photographs, undated; 0 See Container Summary 4 folders (Box 221)
    - Photographs, circa 1990 (Box 226)
    - Theatrical programs, 2011-2013 (Box 221)
    - Lapel pin from the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences, 1971 (Box 227)
  - Diaries and notebooks, 3.0 Linear Feet (4 boxes)
    Includes Larry Kramer personal diaries and calendars, as well as a number of notebooks used to record financial information, addresses and phone numbers.
    - Appointment/daybook, 1960 (Box 222)
    - Appointment/daybook, 1961 (Box 222)
    - Appointment/daybooks, 1962 (Box 222)
    - Diary, 1963 (Box 222)
    - Diary, 1964 (Box 223)
    - Diary, 1965 (Box 223)
    - Appointment/daybook, 1966 (Box 223)
    - Record/address books, undated; 0 See Container Summary (2 folders) (Box 223)
    - Appointment/daybooks, 1967-1997; 0 See Container Summary (14 notebooks) (Box 224)
    - Appointment daybooks, 1997-2004; 0 See Container Summary (5 notebooks) (Box 225)
  - Computer media, 1.25 Linear Feet (1 box)
    - Internal hard drive (Mac 95), [?]-8 November 2011
      - Mac 95 HD ending 8 Nov 11, 2017-ycal-0008-0001; 1 Internal Hard Drives (Box 228)
  - Audiovisual materials, 1.25 Linear Feet (1 box)
    - "One Angry Man: Larry Kramer" Nightline episode, 2001 (Box 229)
- July 2019 Acquisition, 1941-2019; 16.8 Linear Feet (26 boxes) + 1 broadside
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Purchased from Larry Kramer on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2019.
  Organized into five series: Writings, Correspondence, AIDS Activism Files, Personal Papers, and Computer and Audiovisual Media.
  During processing, the majority of press clippings collected by Arthur Kramer were interfiled with Larry Kramer's collection of clippings in Personal Papers. Clippings that were easily identifiable as Arthur's remained part of the Arthur Kramer sub-group.
  The July 2019 Acquisition contains writings, correspondence, AIDS activism files, research files, personal papers, audio and video recordings, digital files, and other papers by and relating to Larry Kramer. It also includes family papers inherited from his brother Arthur Kramer.
  - Writings, 9.1 Linear Feet (12 boxes)
    Writings consists of notes, drafts, research materials, reviews, advertising materials, ephemera, clippings, correspondence, and related materials pertaining to Kramer's novels, screenplays, plays, articles, essays, speeches, and other works.
    Organized into four groupings: Books, Screenplays, Plays, and Shorter Works and Other Writings. Each is arranged alphabetically by title of work.
    - Books
      Includes materials related to Faggots (1978), The American People: Volume 1: Search for My Heart (2015) and The American People: Volume 2: The Brutality of Fact (2020).
      - The American People
        - "City of Death" (working title), early draft, typescript, corrected, [1980s?] (Box 237)
        - Background materials, including draft fragments, holograph, typescript, and typescript printouts, corrected, [1980s?], 1995–2000, undated; 5 folders (Box 237)
        - Research binder with holograph and typescript notes and draft fragments, 1977–2016, undated; 12 folders (Box 242)